{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A distributed database has which of the following advantages over a centralized database?", "opta": "Software cost", "optb": "Software complexity", "optc": "Slow Response", "optd": "Modular growth", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An autonomous homogenous environment is which of the following?", "opta": "The same DBMS is at each node and each DBMS works independently.", "optb": "The same DBMS is at each node and a central DBMS coordinates database access.", "optc": "A different DBMS is at each node and each DBMS works independently.", "optd": "A different DBMS is at each node and a central DBMS coordinates database access.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A transaction manager is which of the following?", "opta": "Maintains a log of transactions", "optb": "Maintains before and after database images", "optc": "Maintains appropriate concurrency control", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Location transparency allows for which of the following?", "opta": "Users to treat the data as if it is at one location", "optb": "Programmers to treat the data as if it is at one location", "optc": "Managers to treat the data as if it is at one location", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A heterogeneous distributed database is which of the following?", "opta": "The same DBMS is used at each location and data are not distributed across all nodes.", "optb": "The same DBMS is used at each location and data are distributed across all nodes.", "optc": "A different DBMS is used at each location and data are not distributed across all nodes.", "optd": "A different DBMS is used at each location and data are distributed across all nodes.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Some of the columns of a relation are at different sites is which of the following?", "opta": "Data Replication", "optb": "Horizontal Partitioning", "optc": "Vertical Partitioning", "optd": "Horizontal and Vertical Partitioning", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is true concerning a global transaction?", "opta": "The required data are at one local site and the distributed DBMS routes requests as necessary.", "optb": "The required data are located in at least one nonlocal site and the distributed DBMS routes requests as necessary.", "optc": "The required data are at one local site and the distributed DBMS passes the request to only the local DBMS.", "optd": "The required data are located in at least one nonlocal site and the distributed DBMS passes the request to only the local DBMS.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A homogenous distributed database is which of the following?", "opta": "The same DBMS is used at each location and data are not distributed across all nodes.", "optb": "The same DBMS is used at each location and data are distributed across all nodes.", "optc": "A different DBMS is used at each location and data are not distributed across all nodes.", "optd": "A different DBMS is used at each location and data are distributed across all nodes.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Replication should be used when which of the following exist?", "opta": "When transmission speeds and capacity in a network prohibit frequent refreshing of large tables.", "optb": "When using many nodes with different operating systems and DBMSs and database designs.", "optc": "The application's data can be somewhat out-of-date.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Storing a separate copy of the database at multiple locations is which of the following?", "opta": "Data Replication", "optb": "Horizontal Partitioning", "optc": "Vertical Partitioning", "optd": "Horizontal and Vertical Partitioning", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A distributed database is which of the following?", "opta": "A single logical database that is spread to multiple locations and is interconnected by a network", "optb": "A loose collection of file that is spread to multiple locations and is interconnected by a network", "optc": "A single logical database that is limited to one location.", "optd": "A loose collection of file that is limited to one location.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A semijoin is which of the following?", "opta": "Only the joining attributes are sent from one site to another and then all of the rows are returned.", "optb": "All of the attributes are sent from one site to another and then only the required rows are returned.", "optc": "Only the joining attributes are sent from one site to another and then only the required rows are returned.", "optd": "All of the attributes are sent from one site to another and then only the required rows are returned.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of replication?", "opta": "Reduced network traffic", "optb": "If the database fails at one site, a copy can be located at another site.", "optc": "Each site must have the same storage capacity.", "optd": "Each transaction may proceed without coordination across the network.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A distributed database can use which of the following strategies?", "opta": "Totally centralized at one location and accessed by many sites", "optb": "Partially or totally replicated across sites", "optc": "Partitioned into segments at different sites", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not one of the stages in the evolution of distributed DBMS?", "opta": "Unit of work", "optb": "Remote unit of work", "optc": "Distributed unit of Work", "optd": "Distributed request", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}